Lev Ki

Software Engineer, Game Developer

Warsaw, Poland. Open to relocation lev.ki.contact@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/lev-ki/

Passionate and experienced game programmer with a strong background in both AAA and indie game development since 2015. I have strong organizational skills that help me with my own work as well as in group settings. I have worked as a Scrum Master in one of my teams.

I am self-motivated, a fast learner, always advocating for transparent communication, and fostering a positive team environment to ensure long-term success.

Experience

CD Projekt Red, Poland (February 2021 - Present)

The Witcher 4 - (January 2024 - Present) Gameplay Programmer (Unreal Engine 5, C++)

- Owning, designing, and developing new gameplay features using C++ and Blueprints
- Setting up and owning Functional Tests
- Creating tools for designers with focus on UX and smooth content creation

Cyberpunk 2077: Phantom Liberty And 2.0 Update (July 2022 - January 2024)

Gameplay Programmer (REDengine 4, C++)

- Owned and delivered gameplay features such as Perk Trees and Cyberware, which were universally praised by both journalists and players
- Participated in game design discussions
- Supported my team as a Scrum Master

GWENT: The Witcher Card Game - (February 2021 - July 2022)

UI and Network Programmer (Unity, C#)

- Developed UI and Client-Side Network features of the game (C#)
- Owned technical design and development of one of the game modes
- Improved CI/CD processes with automation which led to smoother releases fewer issues

Relocation to Poland

Codee.Studio, Russia - (February 2020 - November 2020)

Multiple outsource projects

Game Developer (Unity, C#)

- Delivered an interactive product demonstration for a larger-scale third party
- Had multiple responsibilities, including programming, 3D modeling, level and game design

Independent Game Development (2015 - Present)

As an independent game developer, I have been creating games in my free time and through game jams, working in teams of different sizes, as well as having solo projects

Skills

Programming: C++, C#, C, Python, Java, JS. Multiple other languages

Game Engines: Unreal Engine, Unity, REDengine 4, Godot

Other Skills: Game Design, Organization, Leadership, Teamwork, Communication, Scrum, Level

Design, 3D modeling

Languages: English, Russian

Education & Other Info

- Bachelor's Degree, Computer Science Bauman Moscow State Technical University, Russia Specialization: Robotics and Complex Automation, CAD (Computer-Aided Design) Bachelor's Thesis: Training Continuous Neural Networks Using Optimal Control Methods
- Professional Agile Leadership I (PAL I) certificate

Up-to-date version: https://lev-ki.github.io/Resume/